export default {
  title: "F1 World Champions",
  items: [
    {
      front: "1950",
      back: "Giuseppe Farina",
    },
    {
      front: "1951",
      back: "Juan Manuel Fangio",
    },
    {
      front: "1952",
      back: "Alberto Ascari",
    },
    {
      front: "1953",
      back: "Alberto Ascari",
    },
    {
      front: "1954",
      back: "Juan Manuel Fangio",
    },
    {
      front: "1955",
      back: "Juan Manuel Fangio",
    },
    {
      front: "1956",
      back: "Juan Manuel Fangio",
    },
    {
      front: "1957",
      back: "Juan Manuel Fangio",
    },
    {
      front: "1958",
      back: "Mike Hawthorn",
    },
    {
      front: "1959",
      back: "Jack Brabham",
    },
    {
      front: "1960",
      back: "Jack Brabham",
    },
    {
      front: "1961",
      back: "Phil Hill",
    },
    {
      front: "1962",
      back: "Graham Hill",
    },
    {
      front: "1963",
      back: "Jim Clark",
    },
    {
      front: "1964",
      back: "John Surtees",
    },
    {
      front: "1965",
      back: "Jim Clark",
    },
    {
      front: "1966",
      back: "Denny Hulme",
    },
    {
      front: "1967",
      back: "Denny Hulme",
    },
    {
      front: "1968",
      back: "Graham Hill",
    },
    {
      front: "1969",
      back: "Jackie Stewart",
    },
    {
      front: "1970",
      back: "Jochen Rindt",
    },
    {
      front: "1971",
      back: "Jackie Stewart",
    },
    {
      front: "1972",
      back: "Emerson Fittipaldi",
    },
    {
      front: "1973",
      back: "Jackie Stewart",
    },
    {
      front: "1974",
      back: "Emerson Fittipaldi",
    },
    {
      front: "1975",
      back: "Niki Lauda",
    },
    {
      front: "1976",
      back: "James Hunt",
    },
    {
      front: "1977",
      back: "Niki Lauda",
    },
    {
      front: "1978",
      back: "Mario Andretti",
    },
    {
      front: "1979",
      back: "Jody Scheckter",
    },
    {
      front: "1980",
      back: "Alan Jones",
    },
    {
      front: "1981",
      back: "Nelson Piquet",
    },
    {
      front: "1982",
      back: "Keke Rosberg",
    },
    {
      front: "1983",
      back: "Nelson Piquet",
    },
    {
      front: "1984",
      back: "Niki Lauda",
    },
    {
      front: "1985",
      back: "Alain Prost",
    },
    {
      front: "1986",
      back: "Alain Prost",
    },
    {
      front: "1987",
      back: "Nelson Piquet",
    },
    {
      front: "1988",
      back: "Ayrton Senna",
    },
    {
      front: "1989",
      back: "Alain Prost",
    },
    {
      front: "1990",
      back: "Ayrton Senna",
    },
    {
      front: "1991",
      back: "Ayrton Senna",
    },
    {
      front: "1992",
      back: "Nigel Mansell",
    },
    {
      front: "1993",
      back: "Alain Prost",
    },
    {
      front: "1994",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "1995",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "1996",
      back: "Damon Hill",
    },
    {
      front: "1997",
      back: "Jacques Villeneuve",
    },
    {
      front: "1998",
      back: "Mika Häkkinen",
    },
    {
      front: "1999",
      back: "Mika Häkkinen",
    },
    {
      front: "2000",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "2001",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "2002",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "2003",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "2004",
      back: "Michael Schumacher",
    },
    {
      front: "2005",
      back: "Fernando Alonso",
    },
    {
      front: "2006",
      back: "Fernando Alonso",
    },
    {
      front: "2007",
      back: "Kimi Räikkönen",
    },
    {
      front: "2008",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2009",
      back: "Jenson Button",
    },
    {
      front: "2010",
      back: "Sebastian Vettel",
    },
    {
      front: "2011",
      back: "Sebastian Vettel",
    },
    {
      front: "2012",
      back: "Sebastian Vettel",
    },
    {
      front: "2013",
      back: "Sebastian Vettel",
    },
    {
      front: "2014",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2015",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2016",
      back: "Nico Rosberg",
    },
    {
      front: "2017",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2018",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2019",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2020",
      back: "Lewis Hamilton",
    },
    {
      front: "2021",
      back: "Max Verstappen",
    },
    {
      front: "2022",
      back: "Max Verstappen",
    },
    {
      front: "2023",
      back: "Max Verstappen",
    },
  ],
};
